https://www.weatherbys.com/privacy-notice/

Privacy Policy - Weatherby’s Fishing and Hunting Lodge
Skip to content 877-796-5558|Info@Weatherbys.com
LODGING & DININGRATESSPECIALSENTER TO WINFAMILY FISHING VACATIONFISHINGGRAND LAKE STREAMFLY FISHINGSMALLMOUTH BASSFAMILY FISHING VACATIONMAINE GUIDESICE-OUT TROLLINGFLY BOXST CROIX RIVERWEST BRANCH -PENOBSCOT RIVERGEAR FOR YOUR FISHING TRIPFISHING REPORTSGRAND LAKE STREAM REPORTDOWNEAST LAKES REPORTSTREAM FLOWSMAGAZINE ARTICLESFLY FISHING SCHOOLSLEARN TO FLY FISHWOMEN’S FLY FISHING SCHOOLHUNTINGUPLAND HUNTSGROUSE AND WOODCOCKNORTHWOODS GROUSE CAMPBIRD DOG DAYSGEAR FOR UPLAND HUNTSBIG GAME HUNTSWHITETAIL DEER HUNTSMOOSE HUNTSMAINE GUIDESPLAN A TRIPGETTING HEREDRIVING DIRECTIONSCHARTER PLANE SERVICESCOMMERCIAL FLIGHTSABOUT WEATHERBY’SHISTORY OF WEATHERBY’SMAGAZINE ARTICLESBLOGCONTACT USREQUEST A BROCHUREVIDEOSFAQMAINE VACATIONNATIONAL PARKS AND MONUMENTSBIRDING AND WILDLIFEDOWNEAST MAINEMAINE CONSERVATION EFFORTSGEAR FOR YOUR TRIPPACK FOR UPLAND HUNTPACK FOR FISHING TRIPFILL YOUR FLY BOXHIRE A GUIDERATESLODGING RATESLODGING SPECIALSRESERVATIONS
Search for:
LODGING & DININGRATESSPECIALSENTER TO WINFAMILY FISHING VACATIONFISHINGGRAND LAKE STREAMFLY FISHINGSMALLMOUTH BASSFAMILY FISHING VACATIONMAINE GUIDESICE-OUT TROLLINGFLY BOXST CROIX RIVERWEST BRANCH -PENOBSCOT RIVERGEAR FOR YOUR FISHING TRIPFISHING REPORTSGRAND LAKE STREAM REPORTDOWNEAST LAKES REPORTSTREAM FLOWSMAGAZINE ARTICLESFLY FISHING SCHOOLSLEARN TO FLY FISHWOMEN’S FLY FISHING SCHOOLHUNTINGUPLAND HUNTSGROUSE AND WOODCOCKNORTHWOODS GROUSE CAMPBIRD DOG DAYSGEAR FOR UPLAND HUNTSBIG GAME HUNTSWHITETAIL DEER HUNTSMOOSE HUNTSMAINE GUIDESPLAN A TRIPGETTING HEREDRIVING DIRECTIONSCHARTER PLANE SERVICESCOMMERCIAL FLIGHTSABOUT WEATHERBY’SHISTORY OF WEATHERBY’SMAGAZINE ARTICLESBLOGCONTACT USREQUEST A BROCHUREVIDEOSFAQMAINE VACATIONNATIONAL PARKS AND MONUMENTSBIRDING AND WILDLIFEDOWNEAST MAINEMAINE CONSERVATION EFFORTSGEAR FOR YOUR TRIPPACK FOR UPLAND HUNTPACK FOR FISHING TRIPFILL YOUR FLY BOXHIRE A GUIDERATESLODGING RATESLODGING SPECIALSRESERVATIONS
Search for:
LODGING & DININGRATESSPECIALSMAINE FISHINGMAINE HUNTINGFAMILY FISHING VACATIONSRESERVATIONS
Privacy Notice
Privacy Noticeadmin2019-12-08T00:46:49-05:00Weatherby’s Privacy NoticeOur Commitment To Privacy
Your privacy is important to us. To better protect your privacy we provide this notice explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used.The Information We Collect:
This notice applies to all information collected or submitted on the Weatherby’s website. On some pages, you can order products, make requests, and register to receive materials. The types of personal information collected at these pages are:NameAddressEmail addressPhone numberCredit/Debit Card InformationThe Way We Use Information:
We use the information you provide about yourself when placing an order only to complete that order. We do not share this information with outside parties except to the extent necessary to complete that order.We use the information you provide about someone else when placing an order only to ship the product and to confirm delivery. We do not share this information with outside parties except to the extent necessary to complete that order.We use return email addresses to answer the email we receive. Such addresses are not used for any other purpose and are not shared with outside parties.We use non-identifying and aggregate information to better design our website and to share with advertisers. For example, we may tell an advertiser that X number of individuals visited a certain area on our website, or that Y number of men and Z number of women filled out our registration form, but we would not disclose anything that could be used to identify those individuals.Finally, we never use or share the personally identifiable information provided to us online in ways unrelated to the ones described above without also providing you an opportunity to opt-out or otherwise prohibit such unrelated uses.Our Commitment To Data Security
To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the correct use of information, we have put in place appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.How You Can Access Or Correct Your Information
You can access all your personally identifiable information that we collect online and maintain by logging in to your account and clicking the links to view your address and account information. We use this procedure to better safeguard your information.You can correct factual errors in your personally identifiable information by sending us a request that credibly shows error.To protect your privacy and security, we will also take reasonable steps to verify your identity before granting access or making corrections.How To Contact Us
Should you have other questions or concerns about these privacy policies, please contact us.
112 Milford Road, Grand Lake Stream, MainePhone: 1-877-796-5558
© Copyright 2000 -  Weatherby's Resort | All Rights Reserved 112 Milford Road
Grand Lake Stream, Maine 04668 |
877-796-5558
Privacy PolicyfacebooktwitterinstagramyoutubeEmail
Toggle Sliding Bar Area
